Meet Victor. Over the last six
years, he has created multiple seven-figure businesses
and become one of the youngest
multi-millionaires in all of Houston, Texas.
When Victor was 19 years old, he was
down to zero dollars in his bank account,
but through learning the game
of entrepreneurship at 26 years old,
he now has a net worth over 10 million dollars.
I flew out to Houston, Texas to ask Victor the
number one thing that has enabled him to go
from a one to 10 million dollar net worth.
Understanding that money is a game. It's
a game of numbers. A lot of people,
they get overwhelmed by seeing like that million
dollar figure when all you have to do is.
In this interview, Victor revealed to me
the blueprint that he created to grow
multiple seven-figure businesses across different industries
as a young entrepreneur in today's
world. One car can turn into two, two turns
into four, four turns into a fleet, man. You know,
you wake up, you get to drive whatever
car you want. We have like multiple warehouses,
so we can't keep all the cars
at one warehouse because there's just so many.
His story of how he beat the odds
is an inspiring one to say the least.
I'm James Dumoulin, and this is Questions with Millionaires.
What's been the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
A single year? In a year? I
think this year would probably be that number.
We're halfway through the year, I'm at six million.
Six million for the year. That is incredible, man.
How old were you when you started your first business?
I started my first business when I was 19.
And what was it?
It was my brand for the low clothing.
So like kind of e-commerce?
Yeah, e-commerce.
For people starting on e-commerce today, for
you personally, what was the biggest thing
that you really implemented throughout your brand?
To set yourself apart from the competition.
E-commerce can be a very competitive industry.
A lot of people trying to make apparel brands.
What was your secret to really
standing out in a competitive industry?
It kind of goes back
to like the fail fast method.
I would drop clothes literally every week, whether
they were good or bad or, you know,
whatever, sales, it didn't matter.
I was just dropping to stay in front of
people, where most people, they hold on to a project
for six months, perfect it, tweak it.
But what you have to understand is there's
so many distractions going on on social media.
Nobody's waiting for six months for your big project.
So when you're dropping every week or twice
a week, people just keep seeing you and then
it becomes normal and you
become a part of their algorithm.
You know what I mean?
So that's what put me like on the next level
because I was in front of people on a daily
basis.
Right.
A lot of people, they'll have a great idea.
They'll start that business, but
they really struggle to scale it.
How have you been able to turn
six into seven figures as an entrepreneur?
What's the secret of being able
to scale from six to seven figures?
Um, understanding that money is a game.
It's a game of doubles.
Um, it's a game of numbers.
A lot of people, they get overwhelmed by
seeing like that million dollar figure when all you
have to do is make 10,000, 10 times to get
to a hundred and then make a hundred, 10 times
to get to a million.
So you just got to take
it one figure at a time.
Like I said, team or no team, I never
used any ads or any budget to necessarily propel
my work.
I feel like it was more like bootstrapping
and just knowing that I'm in the field every
single day and whatever battle it is, whatever.
What opponent we face, we just have
to understand that we got to show up.
So consistency was everything.
Consistency.
I love it.
When it comes to sales though, what's
been your secret to sales throughout your career?
Like if you have a potential client or a
customer, maybe they're on the fence and they're leaning
towards a no, what's your strategy to
really turn a no into a yes?
And what's been your, what's your
best sales advice for anybody out there?
Don't push.
Cause when you push, it makes
them seem like you need them.
But in a sense, you want to make it
seem like you don't, you know what I mean?
Because if you're pushing, pushing, pushing.
They're going to be like, Whoa, like I
feel a little, you know, it's strange when someone
comes to your house trying to sell you something, right?
I'd rather be so good and so massive
that people come to me and I'm selecting who's
able.
Yeah.
You get what I mean?
So we was able to actually scale
that out into like an elite program.
And we actually had a subscription for people
who are paying the subscription to get onto
the website earlier than everybody else.
What's been the importance of surrounding
yourself with the right people throughout
your career?
How have you been able to leverage?
Relationships in the business world as an entrepreneur?
What's been your secret to maintaining those relationships?
Man, it's huge.
I think besides consistency network is like
the most important thing because they always
say you're a product, your environment.
And I 100% believe that if I wasn't
putting myself around the right people or what it
wasn't feeling challenged by my circle, then
I would feel like I've already accomplished
everything that I need to do.
You know, I always want to be around
people who are doing what I'm doing or more.
But if I'm around people who
are doing less than what I'm doing.
Then I'm a feel like, okay, like this is
a good ending point for me when I'm just in
the wrong room.
For people out there who may
struggle with networking and building relationships, maybe
they don't know how to like get into
the right doors, get around the right people.
What's your advice to those people?
Like when you were first kind of starting
out, how did you go about building the relationships
that helped you kind of propel in the business world?
Um, I think focusing on yourself and investing
in yourself is the biggest, easiest way to
get into those rooms.
So instead of going into the room with
your handout, you're going into the room with something
to offer.
So when somebody may have more money than
you, more success than you, but if you have
a skill that you've been sharpening that they may
lack, you can fit in like a puzzle and
be like, Hey, I see you've done
X, Y, Z, but you're missing this.
I'm an expert in this.
This is what I have to offer you
instead of, Oh, I see you've done this.
Can you help me do it?
They're going to be like, I don't
have time to help you do this.
But if you can obviously, you know,
exchange something that's mutually beneficial and y'all
may be able to scale business in a different way.
Yeah.
What would you say is the best
financial advice you ever received throughout your
lifetime?
If there's one lesson about money that someone
taught you, maybe a mentor that someone taught
you, what would you say that is?
And like, what's that advice that you'd
pass on to the younger generation today?
Shout out to my guy, Chris Johnson.
I had to say, get money by income.
Yeah.
What that means is whatever money that you
receive, use it to buy assets that make you
more money.
So it's like you get money
and then you buy more money.
Yeah.
So I think that that's probably
like the best advice I've ever given.
Absolutely.
What's the biggest mindset change in
your opinion to become a multimillionaire?
Like if there was a mindset shift.
That people need to have, or maybe not
just necessarily mindset, but if it's a habit that
you've seen consistently throughout yourself and
other people around you, what would you
say is the biggest mindset change or
habit that it takes to become a multimillionaire?
Discipline and careful selection with
what you use your time on.
I think time is worth more than money.
So if you want to amass like a great
amount of wealth, I think you have to leverage your
time more than anything.
And it's so easy to pick the easy.
You're things are more fun things, the
things that, you know, are more attractive looking
versus the boring, consistent and simple things.
But those are the things that
get you to the next level.
So just being more like
selective and decisive and disciplined.
Yeah.
What do you think is the number one
most important skill that every young entrepreneur should
learn in today's world?
Social media marketing, social media marketing.
I think social media marketing
is like the number one catalyst.
If you're trying to scale a business from
zero to a million, social media is not going
anywhere.
And if you want to get in
front of people for like an expensive amount.
Yeah.
Knowing how to market yourself is
going to get you whatever you need.
Yeah.
You had to start from zero, right?
Everything was taken from you.
Your bank account hit zero tomorrow.
What's the first step that you would take
to really build your empire back and become
financially free again?
I think the best part about having a solid
network is I'll just call one of my friends
and be like, yo, loan me 10 grand.
I'm going to just run the whole play again.
Probably start a short form business, car
detailing or something like that, just to
stack up my funds and keep my hands busy.
You know, obviously, once I stack that
up, then I can dive back into.
Like digital, digital real estate.
For sure.
How do you really want to be remembered?
I want to be I
want to have a wider reach.
I feel like what I'm doing is
kind of going under the radar right now.
But in five years, I want to be a
household name, but known for like helping other people
like change their financial financial career and,
you know, just help people learn how
to make money and learn
more things about business and entrepreneurship.
I love it.
So I guess where can everybody find you?
Social media handles is.
G.O.A.T.
Underscore V.I.C.C.
So go big.
That's my handle universally.
Absolutely.
Every platform.
Cool, guys.
Thank you so much for tuning in.
This is 10 questions with a millionaire.
Be sure to leave a like and subscribe for tons
of amazing content and click here to watch us ask a
commercial real estate multimillionaire
how he became wealthy.